So the next step is, we're going to come to the ironing board and we're going to mark our side seams.
And so the sides are the short pieces here.
We're going to do a nice half inch roll and steaming it so it stays nice and firm because we don't want to have to come back and do that.
The steam is going to help set the crease in the fabric so when you sew it you don't have to use pins as much.
Okay, once you get the first half inch crease in, you're going to go back to the top, you should always press in the same direction.
And when we're pressing, we're actually pressing with the iron not sliding it.
I'll show you in just a second.
Now we're going to do a second crease and it's going to be a three quarter inch crease.
So you're actually wanting to pick the iron up and press down on it, not slide it, and go to the other side and do same thing making sure that you have the rolls going both in the same side.
So we're going to roll this direction, towards me so on the finished product you don't have one seam in and one seam out.